BURAK ÇETIN

Software & Game Developer

SKILLS

General Knowledge OOP Data Structures & Algorithms Game Development AI & Machine Learning Robotics&Electronics Competitive Programming Highly Experienced C/C++ Unity3D Unix Shell C# Java Photoshop (Drawing) **Experienced** JavaScript Photoshop (Graphic Design) Arduino & Electronic Components Unity (Custom Editors) Knowledged HTML5 CSS3 Photoshop (Image Manipulation) Basic Knowledge Flixel LaTeX Python .NET Haxe PHP

AWARDS & PARTICIPATIONS



- Silver Medal 2015 (Top 6)
- Bronze Medal 2014 (Top 18)
- Bronze Medal 2013 (Top 18)



- National Olympiads Summer Courses 2013,2014,2015
- International Olympiads Winter Courses 2014,2015,2016

Global Game Jam 2017 & 2018

 Participated at the jam site GGJEGE. (globalgamejam.org/users/clutterarranger)

TUBITAK National Middle School Mathematic Olympiads

• Silver Medal - 2012 (Top 8)

Online Game Jams

• Regularly participating in online accelerated game development events like Ludum Dare. (mantlair.itch.io)

PROFILE

I am a second year undergraduate student with a competitive programming background and self-taught Unity3D knowledge. I want to gain work experience on software and game development.

I am also willing to improve myself on different areas related to the field, like hardware or web development.

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

Unity3D Game Development Workshop - Instructor

Koc University IEEE Club

Cotober 2017

Bogazici University IT Club (CompeC)

October 2017 and November 2016

Bahcesehir University IEEE Club

m December 2017

☐ Computer Engineering 150 Courses - Assistant

Bogazici University Engineering Faculty

Ctober 2016 - Present

Intermediate C Lessons to 9th & 10th Graders - Teacher

Izmir Science High School

2013 - 2015

PROJECTS

Tag Rocket (October 2016)

Developed and released an infinite sidescroller game for mobile, named "Tag Rocket", for a CompeC event.

KTANE Mod Developing

Developed several game mods for Steam game "Keep Talking and Nobody Explodes". (Source codes available on GitHub)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering Bogazici University, Istanbul - Turkey

September 2016 - Present

LANGUAGES

English Turkish French



HOBBIES

Videogames Hiking Woodworking

Drawing Arduino Sports Climbing